Guide to the Service Employees International Union Local 585 Records, 1966-1989 AIS.1982.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Chapter Files: Education, I.
  - School Districts, 1.
    - Franklin School District - Transfer from Local #227, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Franklin School District - Chapter Meetings/Officers, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Franklin School District - Membership/Dues, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Franklin School District - Job Postings/Descriptions, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Franklin School District - Gender Discrimination Settlement, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Franklin School District - Disciplines, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Franklin School District - Dues/Membership, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Franklin School District - Contracts, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Franklin School District - Contracts, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Franklin School District - Employee List, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Franklin School District - Contract, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Franklin School District - Work Schedule, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Franklin School District - Proposed Contract, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Franklin School District - Blue Cross/Dental Plans, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Franklin School District - Job Descriptions, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Franklin School District - Job Classifications/Postings/Scheduling, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Franklin School District - Teachers Strike/Layoffs, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Franklin School District - Retirement/Tool Return, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Franklin School District - Discipline, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Franklin School District - Dues/Prescription Cards, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Franklin School District - Disciplines/Commendations, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Franklin School District - Joe Baker Firing Grievance, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Franklin School District - Negotiations, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Franklin School District - Chapter Internal, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Franklin School District - Disciplines, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Franklin School District - Dues/Scholarships, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Franklin School District - Miscellaneous, 1968-1979 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Gateway School District - Organization/Rivalry: PSEA, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Gateway School District - Organization/Rivalry: PSEA, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Gateway School District - Negotiations, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Gateway School District - Membership/dues, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Gateway School District - Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Gateway School District - Job Assignments, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Gateway School District - Women's Equal Pay Case, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Gateway School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Gateway School District - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Gateway School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Gateway School District - Dues/Membership, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Gateway School District - Dues/Membership, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Gateway School District - Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Gateway School District - Chapter Officers/Meeting Notices, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Gateway School District - Seniority Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Gateway School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Gateway School District - Over-Time, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Gateway School District - Disciplines, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Gateway School District - Contracts, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Gateway School District - Contracts: Teachers/PSEA, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Gateway School District - Seniority, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Gateway School District - Membership/Dues records, A-J, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Gateway School District - Membership/Dues records, K-P, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Gateway School District - Membership/Dues Records, R-Y, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Gateway School District - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Gateway School District - Seniority Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Gateway School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, January-May 8, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Gateway School District - Union Rivalry: PSEA, May 20-31, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Gateway School District - Vacations, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Gateway School District - Miscellaneous, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - General Braddock Public School - School Board Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - General Braddock Public School - School Board Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - General Braddock Public School - School Board Budget, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - General Braddock Public School - School Board Budget, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - General Braddock Public School - Dues/Membership, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - General Braddock Public School - Seniority/Personnel Lists, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - General Braddock Public School - Salary Back Payments, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - General Braddock Public School - Negotiations, 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - General Braddock Public School - Organization, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - General Braddock Public School - Unfair Labor Practices Charge, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - General Braddock Public School - Negotiations, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - General Braddock Public School - Unit Clarification, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - General Braddock Public School - Contracts, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - General Braddock Public School - Contracts, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - General Braddock Public School - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - General Braddock Public School - School District Reorganization, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - General Braddock Public School - Contracts, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - General Braddock Public School - Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - General Braddock Public School - Employee Addresses, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - General Braddock Public School - Disciplines, 1973-1976 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - General Braddock Public School - Officers, 1971-1974 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - General Braddock Public School - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - General Braddock Public School - Seniority List, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - General Braddock Public School - Contract Addenda, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - General Braddock Public School - Contracts: Food Service, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - General Braddock Public School - Contracts: Custodians, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - General Braddock Public School - Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Highlands Public School - Pre-Union Work Contract, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Highlands Public School - Organization, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Highlands Public School - Mailing List, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Highlands Public School - Death Benefits, 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Highlands Public School - Grievances, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Highlands Public School - Negotiations, 1968-1973 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Highlands Public School - Membership Meeting Notices, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Highlands Public School - Dues, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Highlands Public School - Shift Change, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Highlands Public School - Contracts, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Highlands Public School - Contract Proposal, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Highlands Public School - Contracts, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Highlands Public School - Organization, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Highlands Public School - Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 9, Folder 71-72)
    - Highlands Public School - Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Highlands Public School - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 74-75)
    - Highlands Public School - Salary/Seniority List, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Highlands Public School - Employees Manual, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Highlands Public School - Blue Cross Program, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Highlands Public School - Teachers Contract, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Highlands Public School - Contracts, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Highlands Public School - Transfers/Job Bidding, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Highlands Public School - Overtime Procedures, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Highlands Public School - Officers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Highlands Public School - Job Posting, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Highlands Public School - Salary Schedules, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Highlands Public School - Organization: Women Custodians, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Highlands Public School - COLA Re-Opener, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 87)
    - Highlands Public School - Work Issues, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Highlands Public School - Employees Manual, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Highlands Public School - Salary/Seniority List, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 90)
    - Highlands Public School - Negotiations, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 91)
    - Highlands Public School - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 92-93)
    - Highlands Public School - Ratification Ballots, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 94)
    - Highlands Public School - Contracts, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Highlands Public School - Miscellaneous, 1969-1977 (Box 9, Folder 96)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Organization and Authorization Cards, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Negotiations, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - PSEA Contract, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - McMillen Discipline, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Organization, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Negotiations, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Contracts, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Negotiations, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Contracts, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - Jefferson-Dubois Public School - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Contract, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Negotiations, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Dues/Membership, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Sickday Retroactivity, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Hours/Scheduling, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Contracts, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Negotiations, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Cumulative Sickleave Grievance, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 116)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Negotiations, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 117)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - COLA Reovest, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 118)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Contracts, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 119)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Holiday Grievance Arbitration, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 120)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Offices Installation, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Staff Directory, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 122)
    - Jefferson-Morgan Public School - Miscellaneous, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Johnstown Public School - Organization, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Johnstown Public School - Organization, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Johnstown Public School - Confidential Employees, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Johnstown Public School - Contracts, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Johnstown Public School - Local 662 Merger, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Johnstown Public School - Membership Meeting Notices, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Johnstown Public School - Gaydos Grievance, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Johnstown Public School - Contract, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Johnstown Public School - Contract, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Johnstown Public School - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Johnstown Public School - Staff Directory, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Johnstown Public School - Staff Directory/Seniority, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Johnstown Public School - Membership Lists, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Johnstown Public School - Sub-Contracting, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Johnstown Public School - Frieda Oswald Seniority/Sick Days, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Johnstown Public School - Dues/Membership, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Johnstown Public School - Membership Meeting Notices, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Johnstown Public School - Unit Certification Secretaries, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Johnstown Public School - Sub-Contracting, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Johnstown Public School - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Johnstown Public School - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Johnstown Public School - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17-18)
    - Johnstown Public School - Proposed Confidential Employees, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Johnstown Public School - Johnstown Central Labor Council, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Johnstown Public School - Martin Hruinik Seniority Grievance, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Johnstown Public School - Proposed Contract, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Johnstown Public School - Miscellaneous, 1967-1976 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Proposed Contracts, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Contracts, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Contracts, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Membership/Dues/Benefits, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Nadere Frey Discipline, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Employee/Salary List, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Thomas Aruis Discipline Case, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - PSEA Teachers Contract, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Proposed Contract, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Nadere Frey Grievance, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Robert Bartek Seniority Grievance, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Job Bidding/Discrimination, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Negotiations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Officers/Factionalism, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Contracts, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Job Vacancy Notices, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Robert Morrison Job Assignment Grievance, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Dues/Membership, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Negotiations, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Contracts, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Contract Ratification Ballots, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Keystone Oaks Public School - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Dues and Membership, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Employee Lists, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Negotiations, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Grievance Procedure, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Overtime Distribution, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Mary Young Job Bidding Grievance (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Ed Chelcot Scheduling Dispute, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Teacher Salary Analysis, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Officers, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Salary/Seniority List, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Dues and Membership, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Chapter Expenses, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Seria Transfer Grievance Arbitration, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Negotiations, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Dues/Membership, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Dues/Membership, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Membership Meeting Notices, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Political Action/Social Security, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Wolfe Job Bidding Grievance, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Shirley Sick Leave Grievance, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Contracts, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Proposed Contract, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Proposed July Contract, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Negotiations, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Contract, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Job Descriptions (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Kiski Area Public School - Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Latrobe Public School - Contracts, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Latrobe Public School - Organization, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Latrobe Public School - Negotiations, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Latrobe Public School - Dues Questions, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Latrobe Public School - Membership Meeting Notices, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Latrobe Public School - Sub-Contracting Cafeteria, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Latrobe Public School - Salary/Seniority/Mailing Lists, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Latrobe Public School - Attendance Disciplines/Grievances, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Latrobe Public School - Officers, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Latrobe Public School - Henry Membership, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Latrobe Public School - Employment, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Latrobe Public School - Scheduling Grievances, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Latrobe Public School - Wage/Classification Grievances, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Latrobe Public School - Educational Goals Hearings, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Latrobe Public School - Blue Cross Plan, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Latrobe Public School - Salary/Seniority Employment Lists, 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Latrobe Public School - Negotiations: Custodial, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Latrobe Public School - Negotiations: Cafeteria, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 98-99)
    - Latrobe Public School - Grievances, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - Latrobe Public School - Dues Questions, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Latrobe Public School - Officers, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - Latrobe Public School - Cafeteria Employment, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Latrobe Public School - Memorandum of Agreement (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Latrobe Public School - Contracts: Cafeteria, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Latrobe Public School - Contracts: Custodial, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Latrobe Public School - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Organization, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Dues, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Negotiations, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Bus Sub-contracting, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Contracts, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Constitution, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Summer Hours Dispute, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Job Posting, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 115)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Officers, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Pay Stub Dispute, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Meet and Discuss, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Contracts, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Job Descriptions, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Negotiations, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Contract, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Schedules/Duties, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Salary Schedules, 1968-1972 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Dues, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Officers, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Constitution, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Women: Equal Pay, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Holiday Pay Dispute, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Salary/Seniority Lists, 1968-1977 (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Negotiations, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Contracts, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Lay-off Notices, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 133)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Grievances, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Sick Leave Policy, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 135)
    - Leechburg Area Public School District - Miscellaneous, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 136)
    - Mount Lebanon School District - Salary Schedule: Custodians, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Mount Lebanon School District - Organization/Company Union, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Mount Lebanon School District - Organization/Company Union, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Mount Lebanon School District - Company Union Contract, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Mount Lebanon School District - Organization: Secretaries, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)